[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[Apocalypse Log 5]
Don't move.
I can remove the tape, but you have to behave.
You don't want to attract
the zombies back here, do you?
Why did you kidnap me?
Where are you taking me?
I told you, I have something important to do.
What does that have to do with me?
I've been looking for someone important.
That person is you.
We weren't even acquainted before.
And besides, is this how
you treat someone important?
I can't explain everything to you right now.
I need to get you on the road
as soon as possible.
This is the simplest and most direct method.
Explain it to me right now.
If you don't explain it,
we're staying right here.
I'm looking for you because you're an immune.
You have the gene that makes you
immune to the zombie virus.
Immune?
Are you kidding me?
How do you know that?
Well, did you bite yourself here?
- Guang Qi.
- I'm here.
Detect if the target is an immune.
Target confirmed as an immune.
Haven't you ever wondered
why you didn't turn
into a zombie after being bitten?
So, you saved me just because I'm an immune?
Then why didn't you just take me then?
I had to wait for your wound to heal.
Traveling with an injured person
is too much of a burden, huh?
You bastard.
And here I was, trusting you
and thinking we were friends.
What about the others?
What did you do to them?
I had no reason to harm them.
I left a note saying you and I
went out to pick wild fruit.
I've said all I need to say.
Since you're awake now, be wise and follow me.
There will be many dangers on this trip.
Even though you're an immune,
you still won't survive
being torn apart by zombies.
Don't go looking for unnecessary trouble.
Untie my hands.
No.
I need to take a piss.
Are you not even going to
let me relieve myself?
Let go of me, you jerk!
Still trying to run?
No, I'm done running.
If there's a next time, I won't be so polite.
You go first.
What are you up to now?
You're tying me up and
walking me like a dog?
Get in front.
Hey.
Who exactly sent you?
You're looking for an immune?
Your organization must be powerful.
If they're so powerful,
why didn't they send a helicopter?
If you don't want to walk, I can carry you.
But I'll have to tape your mouth shut,
so you don't vomit all over me.
Did you lose contact with your organization?
How much longer do we have to walk?
We can't just keep walking like this.
Even in Journey to the West, they had a horse.
We cross Mount Qianlong first.
My car is parked on the other side.
So, who exactly are you?
A mercenary?
A bounty hunter?
Or something else?
Who is looking for me?
I have the right to know that much.
You'll find out when we get there.
Stop acting so mysterious.
I'm much better off asking a dog.
What now?
I need to pee.
Do it right here.
It's an emergency. Untie me, quick.
I'll help you.
If you don't want to go, keep walking.
Fine, I'll go.
Are you really going to stare?
Fine.
So, you're a pervert.
We're both men. What's the big deal?
Then take yours off and show me.
Fine. You win.
Why did you stop all of a sudden?
It's time to eat.
I'd rather starve to death than eat your food.
What?
You'll just eat anything?
What if you get poisoned?
You're the one who will suffer anyway.
Do whatever you want.
I won't starve without you.
What now?
Lin Zai.
What's wrong with you?
An allergy?
I'm sorry.
Don't go.
Lin Zai.
Hang in there. We'll get you some medicine.
Lin Zai... Lin Zai!
Lin Zai!
[Shanhe Daily]
Lin Zai, you have to hang in there.